<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Mehdi Khoshnoodi</title>
    <link>https://mehdy.me/en/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Mehdi Khoshnoodi</description>
    <image>
      <title>Mehdi Khoshnoodi</title>
      <url>https://mehdy.me/images/avatar.jpg</url>
      <link>https://mehdy.me/images/avatar.jpg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.3</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 10:10:00 +0330</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mehdy.me/en/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Battlefield</title>
      <link>https://mehdy.me/en/posts/2017/05/the-battlefield/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mehdy.me/en/posts/2017/05/the-battlefield/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Battlefield is a project that I&amp;rsquo;ve started in &lt;a href=&#34;http://tehpug.ir&#34;&gt;TehPUG&lt;/a&gt;. you can read the story behind it and see how I decided to start this project &lt;a href=&#34;https://mehdy.me/posts/2017/05/the-tehpug/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far till now I experienced some projects and activities that didn&amp;rsquo;t work out as I expected. I asked my self what are the requirements to activate and motivate TehPUG. I came up with a few answers&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It should be suitable for everyone. from the very beginner that learned something about python today to the python expert. they all should be able to participate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It should be able to engage as many people as possible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It should be endless. it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a project that we do for a while and when it&amp;rsquo;s done it&amp;rsquo;s there are nothing else to do.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It should be fun and attractive and also useful and helpful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So based on these criteria I came up with an idea. A battlefield. A field for robots to fight.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The TehPUG</title>
      <link>https://mehdy.me/en/posts/2017/05/the-tehpug/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mehdy.me/en/posts/2017/05/the-tehpug/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let me introduce &lt;a href=&#34;http://tehpug.ir&#34;&gt;TehPUG&lt;/a&gt;. TehPUG is the Tehran Python Users Group like any other PUG around the world. People who love python or have heard it recently and want to learn more about it. We have meetups every month. Come and join us if you love python too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-little-background&#34;&gt;A little background&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was new to python when I joined TehPUG in its early days. There were people who helped me learn more about python and even give me a chance to do some practical stuffs. I&amp;rsquo;m very grateful to each one of them individually. Time passed by and I integrated more and more with TehPUG and finally became one of it&amp;rsquo;s core member. &lt;strong&gt;Now I had the chance to help others as I was helped&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
